Preliminary Guide to the Joe Szabo Papers and Collection of Original Comic Art, 1960s-2000s SPEC.CGA.JGS
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Lehmkuhl, Vance, 1991-1994 (Box JGS 8, Folder 37)
- Lehner, Rene, circa 1992 (Box JGS 8, Folder 38)
- Lehoczki, Istvan, circa 1989 (Box JGS 8, Folder 39)
- Lenkin, Peter, 1990-1994 (Box JGS 15, Folder 79)
- Leon, Luis Eduardo, circa 1993 (Box JGS 8, Folder 40)
- Leotta, Alfio, circa 1989 (Box JGS 8, Folder 41)
- Lephaft, Pal, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 42)
- Lerche, Doris, 1988 (Box JGS 8, Folder 43)
- Lerner, Arnold, 1981-1986 (Box JGS 8, Folder 44)
- Lesher, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 45)
- Levay, Claudia Marina, 1988 (Box JGS 8, Folder 46)
- Levine, David, 1988-1993 (Box JGS 8, Folder 47)
- Levy, Karen, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 48)
- Lewis, T., 1995 (Box JGS 8, Folder 49)
- Leyden, Jock, 1991-1994 (Box JGS 8, Folder 50)
- Liberati, Bruno, 1986-1987 (Box JGS 8, Folder 51)
- Libin, Ronald 'Bing', 1986-1996 (Box JGS 15, Folder 80, Box JGS 8, Folder 52)
- Lica, Barbu, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 53)
- Licurici, George, circa 1991 (Box JGS 8, Folder 54)
- Liebermann, Erik, 1991-1992 (Box JGS 8, Folder 55)
- Lieberman, Joseph, 1993 (Box JGS 8, Folder 56)
- Lightfoot, M., 1993 (Box JGS 8, Folder 57)
- Lilley, Les, 1986-1997 (Box JGS 8, Folder 58)
- Lin, Moshik, 1993 (Box JGS 8, Folder 59)
- Linek, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 60)
- Ling, Dick, 1987 (Box JGS 8, Folder 61)
- Linkert, Lo, 1987-1995 (Box JGS 8, Folder 62)
- Lionar, Thomas A., undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 63)
- Lipovsky, Milan, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 64)
- Liubich, V.P., 1991 (Box JGS 8, Folder 65)
- Locher, Dick, 1988-1995 (Box JGS 8, Folder 66)
- Locke, John, 1994 (Box JGS 8, Folder 67)
- Loewy, J., 1994 (Box JGS 8, Folder 68)
- Loffler, R., 1991-1992 (Box JGS 8, Folder 69)
- Lohmann, Willy, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 8, Folder 70-71)
- Loiseau, Carlos, 1985 (Box JGS 8, Folder 72)
- London, David, 1992 (Box JGS 8, Folder 73)
- London, Rick, 1991 (Box JGS 8, Folder 74)
- Long, John, 1991 (Box JGS 8, Folder 75)
- Lord, M.G., 1990 (Box JGS 8, Folder 76)
- Lorenz, Lee, 1991 (Box JGS 8, Folder 77)
- Louderback, Dick, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 78)
- Luann, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 79)
- Lucenic, Allan, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 80)
- Ludo, Goderis, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 81)
- Lui-Lengyel, Hongying, 1987-1996 (Box JGS 15, Folder 81)
- Lukyanenko, 1990-1995 (Box JGS 8, Folder 82)
- Lurie, Ranan R., 1986-1993 (Box JGS 8, Folder 83)
- Lutczyu, E., 1992 (Box JGS 8, Folder 84)
- Lynch, Mark, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 8, Folder 85-86)
- Lynde, Stan, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 111)
- Macauley, Don, 1994 (Box JGS 8, Folder 87)
- Machamer, Gene, 1988 (Box JGS 8, Folder 88)
- Macintosh, Craig, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 89)
- Mackenzie, Don, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 90)
- MacNelly, Jeff, 1987-1995 (Box JGS 8, Folder 91)
- Macpherson, 1989 (Box JGS 8, Folder 92)
- Madden, Chris, 1992 (Box JGS 8, Folder 93)
- Madero (Polito), 1988-1998 (Box JGS 8, Folder 94)
- Magano, Jorge L.Z., 1991 (Box JGS 8, Folder 95)
- Magnatti, Carlo, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 8, Folder 96)
- Majevski, J., 1993 (Box JGS 8, Folder 97)
- Majoral, Ignasi, 1990-1999 (Box JGS 8, Folder 98)
- Maley, Matt, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 1)
- Malkoc, Enver, 1995-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 2)
- Mallia, Gorg, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 19, Folder 3)
- Malone, 1992 (Box JGS 19, Folder 4)
- Maloney, Vicki, 1987-1989 (Box JGS 19, Folder 5)
- Malysz, Radoslav, 1990-1991 (Box JGS 19, Folder 6)
- Manczak, E., 1986 (Box JGS 19, Folder 7)
- Manjares, M., 1988 (Box JGS 19, Folder 8)
- Manjunatha, H.B., 1986 (Box JGS 19, Folder 9)
- Marabu, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 10)
- Margolies, Bob, 1990 (Box JGS 19, Folder 11)
- Margulies, J., 1984-1994 (Box JGS 19, Folder 12)
- Marinski, Iako, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 13)
- Marko, 1992-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 14)
- Marlette, Doug, 1985-1991 (Box JGS 19, Folder 15)
- Marsden, Ian David, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 16)
- Martin, Don, 1986-1989 (Box JGS 19, Folder 17)
- Martin, John, 1989-1995 (Box JGS 19, Folder 18)
- Martin, Matthew, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 19)
- Martirena, Alfredo, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 20)
- Martinez, Rincon, circa 1989 (Box JGS 19, Folder 21)
- Mas, Sergio, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 22)
- Masaraci, Kamil, 1993 (Box JGS 19, Folder 23)
- Matawaran, Ely, 1986 (Box JGS 19, Folder 24)
- Matocha, Marian, 1988-1990 (Box JGS 19, Folder 25)
- Mattelaer, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 26)
- Matthews, Tom, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 99)
- Matuska, 1988-1997 (Box JGS 8, Folder 100)
- Mavrov, Kiro, 1986-1991 (Box JGS 8, Folder 101)
- Maynard, Ken, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 102)
- McDonald, Verry, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 1)
- McDonnel, Patrick, 1999 (Box JGS 9, Folder 2)
- McEldowney, Brooke, 1995-2001 (Box JGS 9, Folder 3)
- McGarrm, Steve, 1991 (Box JGS 9, Folder 4)
- McGarry, Steve, 1990-1992 (Box JGS 9, Folder 5)
- McGeean, Ed, 1990 (Box JGS 9, Folder 6)
- McGillicuddy, M., 1991-1995 (Box JGS 15, Folder 82)
- McGruder, Aaron, 2001 (Box JGS 9, Folder 7)
- McGuinness, G., 1995 (Box JGS 9, Folder 8)
- McManus, George, 1944 (Box JGS 9, Folder 9)
- McSherry, K., circa 1991 (Box JGS 9, Folder 10)
- Meder, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 103)
- Medzionis, Saulius, circa 1991 (Box JGS 8, Folder 104)
- Mehrabi, Massoud, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 105)
- Meint, Klaus, 1991 (Box JGS 8, Folder 106)
- Melnik, Leonid, undated (Box JGS 8, Folder 107)
- Mena, Jose L.M., 1993-1995 (Box JGS 8, Folder 108)
- Mercader, Jose, 1987-1989 (Box JGS 8, Folder 110)
- Mercado, James, 1993-1995 (Box JGS 8, Folder 109)
- Messick, Dale, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 27)
- Meyer, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 28)
- Miel, Deng, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 29)
- Miel, Prudencio, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 30)
- Mihailov, Lubomir, 1982-1990 (Box JGS 19, Folder 31)
- Mihatov, Mojmir, 1981 (Box JGS 19, Folder 32)
- Milic, Slobodan, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 33)
- Militaru, Virgil, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 34)
- Militello, Clif, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 35)
- Millard, Ken, 1994 (Box JGS 19, Folder 36)
- Miller, Audrey, 1990 (Box JGS 19, Folder 37)
- Miller, T.R., 1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 38)
- Milorad, Sijan, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 39)
- Miloradovic, Mileta, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 40)
- Mirgasim, Gali, 1988 (Box JGS 19, Folder 41)
- Miriam, M., undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 42)
- Miro, Stefanovic, 1993 (Box JGS 19, Folder 43)
- Misjuk, V.K., circa 1995 (Box JGS 19, Folder 44)
- Miskovic, P., undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 45)
- Mitchell, Bill, 1994 (Box JGS 19, Folder 46)
- Mitrovic, T., undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 47)
- Moebius, 1993 (Box JGS 19, Folder 48)
- Mohammadyari, A.F., 1995 (Box JGS 19, Folder 49)
- Mokhtari, D., 1989-1990 (Box JGS 19, Folder 50)
- Mokievsky, Valentin, 1993-1995 (Box JGS 19, Folder 51)
- Molin, J., undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 52)
- Moolenarr, Ab, 1993-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 53, Box JGS 15, Folder 83)
- Mooros, Dick, 1977 (Box JGS 19, Folder 54)
- Moran, Pablo, A., undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 55)
- Mordillo, 1993 (Box JGS 19, Folder 56)
- Moreno, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 57)
- Morgan, Chris, 1993 (Box JGS 19, Folder 58)
- Morgan, Jay P., 1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 59)
- Morgan, Jeff, 1992 (Box JGS 19, Folder 60)
- Morin, Jim, 1995-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 61)
- Morparia, H., circa 1987 (Box JGS 19, Folder 62)
- Motchalov, Vladimir, 1991 (Box JGS 19, Folder 63)
- Motohashi, Koichi, 1993 (Box JGS 19, Folder 64)
- Mruz, David, circa 1992 (Box JGS 19, Folder 65)
- Muharraqi, A., 1995 (Box JGS 19, Folder 66)
- Mulaomerovic, J., undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 67)
- Munro, Ken, 1993 (Box JGS 19, Folder 68)
- Murat, Alimov, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 69)
- Murphy, Dan, 1993 (Box JGS 19, Folder 70)
- Murray, Joe, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 71)
- Muse, Ken, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 72)
- Muzher, Hani, circa 1988 (Box JGS 19, Folder 73)
- Myer, Andy, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 74)
- Myers, Eugene, undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 75)
- Myers, Russ, 1990 (Box JGS 19, Folder 76)
- Mysyrowicz, W., undated (Box JGS 19, Folder 77)
- Nachev, Stoian, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 11)
- Nadav, No'Am, 1988 (Box JGS 9, Folder 12)
- Namboodiri, 1995 (Box JGS 9, Folder 13)
- Najafi (Mohsen), undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 14)
- Naranjo, 1993 (Box JGS 9, Folder 15)
- Narbutas, A., 1994-1996 (Box JGS 9, Folder 16)
- Nast, Thomas, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 17)
- Nazrul, 1989 (Box JGS 9, Folder 18)
- Neacsu, C., undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 19)
- Neat, Tony, 1987-1993 (Box JGS 9, Folder 20)
- Nelson, Cap, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 21)
- Nelson, Roy Paul, 1994 (Box JGS 9, Folder 22)
- Nemes, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 23)
- Nenashev, Vladimir, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 9, Folder 24)
- Nesbitt, Mark, 1992-1995 (Box JGS 9, Folder 25)
- Ness, Art, 1991-1992 (Box JGS 9, Folder 26)
- Neubecker, Robert, 1988 (Box JGS 9, Folder 27)
- Nicholls, J.C., undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 28)
- Nico, 1988-1992 (Box JGS 9, Folder 29)
- Nicolae, Stoia, 1993 (Box JGS 9, Folder 30)
- Nicolaz, 1993 (Box JGS 9, Folder 31)
- Nicoliello, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 32)
- Nieuwendijk, P., 1988-1996 (Box JGS 9, Folder 33, Box JGS 17, Folder 1)
- Nikitin, Victor, 1991 (Box JGS 9, Folder 34)
- Nilsson, Ulf Ivar, 1991 (Box JGS 9, Folder 35)
- Nirmal, J.R., undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 36)
- Nishida, Toshiko, 1996 (Box JGS 9, Folder 37)
- Nixon, Roy, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 38)
- Norkin, Sam, 1985-1988 (Box JGS 9, Folder 39)
- Norman, Dean, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 40)
- Novosibizsk, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 41)
- Nunez (Nano), undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 42)
- Nunez, J.J.S. (Duduf), 1992 (Box JGS 9, Folder 43)
- Nutzle, 1984-1987 (Box JGS 9, Folder 44)
- Nyberg, Tim, 1985-1989 (Box JGS 9, Folder 45)
- Oba, Hiroshi, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 46)
- O'Connor, John, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 47)
- Odabasioglu, Sezer, 1988 (Box JGS 9, Folder 48)
- Odemark, Tor, 1992 (Box JGS 9, Folder 49)
- Odoi, Frank, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 50)
- O'Hare, Mark, 1999 (Box JGS 9, Folder 51)
- Ohrenschall, Peter, 1989-1990 (Box JGS 9, Folder 52)
- Oktay, Bulent, 1993-1994 (Box JGS 9, Folder 53)
- Oleg, Estis, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 54)
- Olimp, Boros, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 55)
- Oliphant, Pat, 1987-1993 (Box JGS 9, Folder 56)
- Oliphant, Tim, 1985-1993 (Box JGS 9, Folder 57)
- Oliver, Jane J., 1991 (Box JGS 9, Folder 58)
- Olszewski, M., 1985 (Box JGS 9, Folder 59)
- Ong, Guus, 1991 (Box JGS 9, Folder 60)
- Oniszk, Andrew, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 61)
- Ono, Kosei, 1994-1996 (Box JGS 17, Folder 2)
- Oral, Tan, 1984-1994 (Box JGS 9, Folder 62)
- Orekhov, Anatolij, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 63)
- Origone, 1987-1991 (Box JGS 9, Folder 64)
- Ormenisan, M., undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 65)
- O'Rourke, Mike, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 66)
- Ortega, Carlos, 1988 (Box JGS 9, Folder 67)
- Ortiz, Carlos Raul, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 9, Folder 68)
- Ortner, Heinz, 1989-1992 (Box JGS 9, Folder 69)
- Orzuj, Raquel, 1983-1997 (Box JGS 9, Folder 70, Box JGS 17, Folder 3)
- Ostatek, Vadar, circa 1984 (Box JGS 9, Folder 71)
- Oster, 1989 (Box JGS 9, Folder 72)
- Ostergaard, Kurt, 1991-1994 (Box JGS 17, Folder 4)
- Ottey, Steve, 1989-1990 (Box JGS 9, Folder 73)
- Ozbek, Eray, 1989-1999 (Box JGS 9, Folder 74)
- Ozer, Atila, 1994-1995 (Box JGS 9, Folder 75)
- Ozkan, Ismail, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 76)
- Pacella, Mark, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 77)
- Packalen, Leif, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 17, Folder 5, Box JGS 9, Folder 78)
- Padilla, Steve, 1996 (Box JGS 9, Folder 79)
- Padin, Clemente, 1986 (Box JGS 9, Folder 80)
- Pahl, Helmut, 1982-1983 (Box JGS 9, Folder 81)
- Paixao, Sergio, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 82)
- Palka, Dusan, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 83)
- Pallady, Loyal, 1993 (Box JGS 9, Folder 84)
- Palma, Pedro J., 1991-1993 (Box JGS 9, Folder 85)
- Palombella, Nicola, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 86)
- Pancho, 1991 (Box JGS 9, Folder 87)
- Pan Shun Qi, circa 1989 (Box JGS 9, Folder 88)
- Pannozo, Steve, 1987-1996 (Box JGS 9, Folder 89)
- Papai, Gabor, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 9, Folder 90)
- Papapetrou (Pin), 1996 (Box JGS 9, Folder 91)
- Paradkar, Vijay, 1990 (Box JGS 9, Folder 92)
- Parisi, Mark, 1988-1995 (Box JGS 9, Folder 93)
- Park, W.B., 1985-1994 (Box JGS 9, Folder 94)
- Parker, Brant, 1992-1994 (Box JGS 9, Folder 95)
- Parker, Dave, 1993 (Box JGS 9, Folder 96)
- Parn, Priit, 1984 (Box JGS 9, Folder 97)
- Parsons, Jen, 1995 (Box JGS 9, Folder 98)
- Parzyszek, I., undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 99)
- Pascal, D.G., 1991 (Box JGS 9, Folder 100)
- Paschenko, Igor Ivanovich, 1993-1999 (Box JGS 9, Folder 101)
- Patel, J (Rangalo), undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 102)
- Patrascan, Costel, 1991 (Box JGS 9, Folder 103)
- Patten, Frederick, 1986-1997 (Box JGS 17, Folder 6)
- Pauer, Frank, 1993 (Box JGS 9, Folder 104)
- Paul, L.G., 1986 (Box JGS 9, Folder 105)
- Paulus, Gerold, 1987-1995 (Box JGS 9, Folder 106)
- Pavel, C., circa 1995 (Box JGS 9, Folder 107)
- Pavic, Darko, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 1)
- Pavlidis, Vangelis, 1986-1996 (Box JGS 10, Folder 2)
- Pavlik, Vladimir, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 3)
- Pecareff, N., 1990 (Box JGS 9, Folder 108)
- Peck, Everett, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 109)
- Peegel, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 4)
- Peetermans, Jean, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 5)
- Peev, Tsocho, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 6)
- Peichl, Prof. Gustav, 1991-1994 (Box JGS 10, Folder 7)
- Pelaez, Jairo, 1986-1994 (Box JGS 17, Folder 7, Box JGS 10, Folder 8)
- Pena-Pai, Julian, 1987 (Box JGS 10, Folder 9)
- Penev, Plamen, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 10)
- Perkins, Dan, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 10, Folder 11)
- Perles, Claire, 1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 12)
- Permyakov, M., undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 111)
- Pernecky, Bohuslav, 1992-1998 (Box JGS 9, Folder 112)
- Peruzzo, Paolo, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 113)
- Pestana, Mauricio, circa 1993 (Box JGS 9, Folder 114)
- Peters, Mike, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 9, Folder 115)
- Petersen, Teddy, 1993 (Box JGS 9, Folder 117)
- Peterson, Roy, 1989-1995 (Box JGS 9, Folder 116)
- Petricic, Dusan, undated (Box JGS 9, Folder 117)
- Peve, 1995 (Box JGS 9, Folder 118)
- Pfister, Heinz, 1991 (Box JGS 9, Folder 119)
- Pfuschi, 1992 (Box JGS 10, Folder 13)
- Phillips, Jim, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 14)
- Phipps, Dan, 1989 (Box JGS 10, Folder 15)
- Pijet, Andrzej, 1985-1995 (Box JGS 10, Folder 16)
- Pike, Douglas, 1991 (Box JGS 10, Folder 17)
- Pilo (Felix Bravo), 1987-1988 (Box JGS 10, Folder 18)
- Pilozo, Enrique, 1987-1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 19)
- Pinatel, circa 1994 (Box JGS 10, Folder 20)
- Pincham, Dan, 1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 21)
- Pinter, Patrick, 1992-1996 (Box JGS 17, Folder 8, Box JGS 10, Folder 22)
- Pintilie, E., 1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 23)
- Pinto, J.H., undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 24)
- Pinto, Venantius Joseph, 1988 (Box JGS 10, Folder 25)
- Pipes, Steve, 1988-1996 (Box JGS 10, Folder 26)
- Pismestrovic, Petar, 1992-2002 (Box JGS 10, Folder 27)
- Piven, 1999 (Box JGS 10, Folder 28)
- Plantu, 1991-1992 (Box JGS 10, Folder 29)
- Plastyk, Artysta, 1991 (Box JGS 10, Folder 30)
- Plekhanov, I., undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 31)
- Ploegaert, Fr., 1989-1991 (Box JGS 10, Folder 32)
- Plotena, Marie, 1991 (Box JGS 10, Folder 33)
- Plympton, Bill, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 34)
- Podulka, Andrzej, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 35)
- Pohlenz, Bernd, 1984-1986 (Box JGS 10, Folder 36)
- Polanski, Marek, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 37)
- Poll, 1985-1987 (Box JGS 10, Folder 38)
- Polo, Alvaro, 1996 (Box JGS 17, Folder 9)
- Polo Madero, Jose E. (Polito), undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 39)
- Pop-Iliev, Jordan, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 40)
- Pop-Novakov, M., undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 41)
- Popa, Stefan, 1995 (Box JGS 10, Folder 42)
- Pope, Kevin, 1992-1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 43)
- Pope, W.C., undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 44)
- Popescu, Adrian, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 45)
- Popov, Trayko, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 46)
- Popovici, Radu, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 47)
- Porges, Paul Peter, circa 1991 (Box JGS 10, Folder 48)
- Porumbita, Mihaita, 1992-1996 (Box JGS 10, Folder 49)
- Postruzin, Louis (Pol), 1987-1996 (Box JGS 10, Folder 50)
- Pourahmed, F., circa 1996 (Box JGS 10, Folder 51)
- Prasil, Jindro, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 52)
- Preston, Dennis, 1992 (Box JGS 10, Folder 53)
- Preziosi, Don, 1991 (Box JGS 10, Folder 54)
- Price, George, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 55)
- Priggee, Milt, 1988 (Box JGS 10, Folder 56)
- Prince, Winthrop, 1986-1987 (Box JGS 10, Folder 57)
- Printz, Lawrence, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 58)
- Priza, Gopal, 1995 (Box JGS 10, Folder 59)
- Proetto, R.A., undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 60)
- Promchan, Vicha, 1988-1997 (Box JGS 17, Folder 10, Box JGS 10, Folder 61)
- Pryor, Geoff, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 62)
- Pulitzer, Joseph, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 63)
- Puszta, 1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 64)
- Pyatkov, A.V., undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 65)
- Pytlik, Zygmunt, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 66)
- Qi, Pan Shun, 1992 (Box JGS 10, Folder 67)
- Quesado, Toledo, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 68)
- Quinn, Tim, 1987-1988 (Box JGS 10, Folder 69)
- Quino, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 70)
- Quispe, David C.V., 1991-1992 (Box JGS 10, Folder 71)
- Radoslavov, R., 1991 (Box JGS 10, Folder 72)
- Radu, Bercea, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 73)
- Raducanu, Dan, circa 1990 (Box JGS 10, Folder 74)
- Rahmanov, Rustam, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 75)
- Raines, Kathy, 1995 (Box JGS 10, Folder 76)
- Rak, Bella, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 77)
- Raka, Kosta, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 78)
- Rakha, circa 1990 (Box JGS 10, Folder 79)
- Raletz, N., 1990 (Box JGS 10, Folder 80)
- Rall, Ted, 1989-1995 (Box JGS 10, Folder 81)
- Ramamurthy, B.V., 1989 (Box JGS 10, Folder 82)
- Ramirez, 1994-1995 (Box JGS 10, Folder 83)
- Ramli, Secac, 1986-1987 (Box JGS 10, Folder 84)
- Ramoglu, Ziya, 1976-1994 (Box JGS 10, Folder 85)
- Ramos, Marko, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 10, Folder 86)
- Rannih, Vladimir, 1994 (Box JGS 10, Folder 87)
- Raobail, P., 1984-1986 (Box JGS 10, Folder 88)
- Raouf, circa 1995 (Box JGS 10, Folder 89)
- Rapallo, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 90)
- Rashkovich, V., 1992-1996 (Box JGS 10, Folder 91)
- Rau, Tibor, 1996 (Box JGS 10, Folder 92)
- Raues, Gerc, 1982-1986 (Box JGS 10, Folder 93)
- Rauschenbach, Erich, 1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 94)
- Rawls, Sam, 1990 (Box JGS 10, Folder 95)
- Raymond, Alex, 1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 96)
- Reay, Richard, 1984-1987 (Box JGS 10, Folder 97)
- Reddy, Madhu, 1993-1994 (Box JGS 10, Folder 98)
- Redman, Lenn, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 99)
- Reiner, John, 1986-1989 (Box JGS 10, Folder 100)
- Reiter, Voldemar, 1985-1987 (Box JGS 10, Folder 101)
- Reynolds, Jerry, 1987 (Box JGS 10, Folder 102)
- Ric and Roach, 1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 103)
- Ricci, Michael, 1995 (Box JGS 10, Folder 104)
- Ricciardi, S.R., 1990-1991 (Box JGS 10, Folder 105)
- Rich, Lyon, circa 1989 (Box JGS 10, Folder 106)
- Richardson, J.L., 1990 (Box JGS 10, Folder 107)
- Richardson, Sam, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 108)
- Rickard, Jack, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 109)
- Rieszutek, Tomasz, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 110)
- Rifas, Leonard, 1988-1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 111)
- Rigg, Peter, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 112)
- Riho, Unt, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 113)
- Rinco, Jairo Pelaez, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 114)
- Ripke, Don, 1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 115)
- Rippinger, Che, 1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 116)
- Riva, Liviano, 1989-1990 (Box JGS 10, Folder 117)
- Rivandi, M.H., 1991 (Box JGS 10, Folder 118)
- Rivera, Sonya C., 1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 119)
- Rivero, Aldo, 1992 (Box JGS 10, Folder 120)
- Road, Sylvia, undated (Box JGS 10, Folder 121)
- Robbins, Trina, 1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 122)
- Robinson, Jerry, 1972-1991 (Box JGS 10, Folder 123-124)
- Robles, C.R. Ponce, 1992 (Box JGS 10, Folder 125)
- Robylev, Sergei, 1993 (Box JGS 10, Folder 126)
- Rocha, Gonzalo, 1992 (Box JGS 10, Folder 127)
- Rodewalt, Vance, 1990-1991 (Box JGS 10, Folder 128)
- Rodionov, Viktor, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 1)
- Rodriguez, G., 1993-1996 (Box JGS 11, Folder 2, Box JGS 17, Folder 11)
- Rogers, 1988 (Box JGS 11, Folder 3)
- Rogers, Marshall, 1989 (Box JGS 11, Folder 4)
- Rogers, V.C., undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 5)
- Rojas, Manuel Vargas, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 6)
- Rollow, Werner, 1986 (Box JGS 11, Folder 7)
- Ronaldo, 1995 (Box JGS 11, Folder 8)
- Rooshan, 1989 (Box JGS 11, Folder 9)
- Rosandich, Dan, 1989-1991 (Box JGS 11, Folder 10)
- Rosen, Hy, 1987-1990 (Box JGS 11, Folder 11)
- Rosie and Mark, 1990 (Box JGS 11, Folder 12)
- Ross, Larry, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 13)
- Roth, Arnold, 1987-1989 (Box JGS 11, Folder 14)
- Rothco Cartoons, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 15)
- Rousseau, Jean, 1991 (Box JGS 11, Folder 16)
- Rozenberg, D., undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 17)
- Rozental, Izel, 1993-1996 (Box JGS 11, Folder 18)
- Rruizte, 1991 (Box JGS 11, Folder 19)
- Rubin, Leigh, 1985-1988 (Box JGS 11, Folder 20)
- Rubina, Tatjana, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 21)
- Ruoff, Andrea, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 22)
- Russell, Jim, 1987-1995 (Box JGS 11, Folder 23)
- Ruszkai, Gabor, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 24)
- Rzeszutek, T., 1985 (Box JGS 11, Folder 25)
- Saad, Aladin, 1992-1995 (Box JGS 11, Folder 26)
- Sabat, Hermenegildo, 1986-1994 (Box JGS 11, Folder 27)
- Sack, Steve, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 28)
- Sadurski, S., undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 29)
- Sahachat Pocanan, Suchat, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 30)
- Sajdik, Ferenc, 1989 (Box JGS 11, Folder 31)
- Sajtinac, Borislav, 1991 (Box JGS 11, Folder 32)
- Sakai, Seigo, 1995 (Box JGS 11, Folder 33)
- Salamoun, Jiri, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 34)
- Salas(Jano), 1987 (Box JGS 11, Folder 35)
- Salinas, Luis, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 36)
- Saltzman, Tony, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 37)
- Salzman, Richard W., 1987-1988 (Box JGS 11, Folder 38)
- Samachar, Gujrat, 1991 (Box JGS 11, Folder 39)
- San Lim, Chung, 1993-1994 (Box JGS 15, Folder 85)
- Sanders, Bill, 1988 (Box JGS 11, Folder 40)
- Sansom, Erik, 1996 (Box JGS 11, Folder 41)
- Santau, Horia, 1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 42)
- Santiago (Neltair Abreu), 1972-1995 (Box JGS 11, Folder 43)
- Sargent, Ben, 1988 (Box JGS 11, Folder 44)
- Saroukhan, 1989 (Box JGS 11, Folder 45)
- Sasturain (Fierro), 1986 (Box JGS 11, Folder 46)
- Sattler, Dave, 1996 (Box JGS 11, Folder 47)
- Sauceda "McDonald", 1992 (Box JGS 11, Folder 48)
- Sauchea, I.E., 1991 (Box JGS 11, Folder 49)
- Saudek, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 50)
- Sawant, Suresh, 1988-2002 (Box JGS 11, Folder 51, Box JGS 19, Folder 85)
- Sawka, Henryk, 1996 (Box JGs 19, Folder 86)
- Sawyer, Pierre, 1981-1988 (Box JGS 11, Folder 52)
- Scancarelli, 1988-1996 (Box JGS 11, Folder 53)
- Schacherl, R., 1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 54)
- Scheld, Betsy, 1988 (Box JGS 11, Folder 55)
- Schlegel, Wolfgang, circa 1992 (Box JGS 11, Folder 56)
- Schmolze, Paul, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 57)
- Schmuckle, Rudolf, 1992 (Box JGS 11, Folder 58)
- Schmutz, Hormen, 1986 (Box JGS 11, Folder 59)
- Schneider, Howie, 1990 (Box JGS 11, Folder 60)
- Schneider, Jonathan, 1987-1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 61)
- Schopf, Oliver, 1995 (Box JGS 11, Folder 62)
- Schorr, Bill, circa 1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 63)
- Schottke, H., 1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 64)
- Schowalter, Todd, 1992 (Box JGS 11, Folder 65)
- Schreib, Bob, 1994-1996 (Box JGS 11, Folder 66)
- Schulz, Charles, 1988-2002 (Box JGS 11, Folder 67)
- Schwadron, 1988-1994 (Box JGS 11, Folder 68)
- Schwartz, Jill Karla, 1988 (Box JGS 11, Folder 69)
- Schwentzel, F., 1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 70)
- Scott, Jerry, 1988-1992 (Box JGS 11, Folder 71)
- Scudera, Domenick, 1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 72)
- Searle, Ronald, 1989-1997 (Box JGS 11, Folder 73)
- Seavey, David, 1989-1994 (Box JGS 11, Folder 74)
- Seeberg, H.A., 1980-1987 (Box JGS 11, Folder 75)
- Seetongfong, S., 1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 76)
- Selcuk, Turhan, 1956-1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 77)
- Selmeczi, Zsolt, 1990-1991 (Box JGS 11, Folder 78)
- Semerenko, V., undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 79)
- Semiramis, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 80)
- Senn, Martin, 1986 (Box JGS 11, Folder 81)